I want direct to consumer brand. We are doing over five millions per year.
What's profit?
Over 70%. I would like to be in 10 millions per month.
The advice to double the business is different than the advice to 20%.
Which one would you rather me answer?
Double.
I mean, spend more payback.
Okay, so let's go to the other one.
No, no.
Well, your margin is going to start compressing
as you spend more and more dollars in advertising.
The only way you can counteract that
is two things. One is product driven.
You're getting some left word of mouth that
for every one person who buys the bag,
they send you another 0.2 people who send the bag.
So that offsets CAC at scale, which is word of mouth.
The second thing that offsets CAC at scale
is going to be brand reputation,
because you can say whatever you want about yourself
that the product sucks, that will end.
The brand lift that you're going to get,
especially because you're unpaid as your primary,
that you're going to get from being able to whitelist
and have different avatars that already have brand recognition or mutation,
where your stuff is going to be more difficult to calculate,
but I can tell you when it's not there,
is that you won't be able to scale.
So that's what you have to build towards.